John Clarke Slater Papers 1908-1976 Mss.B.SL2p
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1908-1976; 45 lin. feet (Box 1-89)
  - Crawford, Franzo H
  - Crawford, Victor A
  - Creasy, James V, Jr.
  - Creutz, E
  - Cribier, D
  - Cropper, William H
  - Crowell, Thomas Y., Company
  - Crowley, J W
  - Cruetz, E
  - Cruickshank, D W J
  - CSIRO
  - Csizmadia, Imre G
  - Cummings, Lew A., Company
  - Cummings, Mel W
  - Curien, H
  - Curl, Robert F
  - Curletti, Giuseppe
  - Current papers in physics
  - Curtis, Charles P
  - Cusachs, Louis Chopin
  - Cusick, Paul V
  - Cussen, Arthur J
  - Cutler, Melvin
  - Cutler, Paul
  - Czechoslovak Academy of Sciences
  - D, Karl K.
    - Basis of thermodynamics, with illustrations from magnetism
  - Dado, Genevieve
  - Dahl, Jens Peder
  - Dalgarno, Alec
  - Dalven, Richard
  - Damascelli, N
  - Danese, J B
  - Daniel, Emile
  - Danielson, G C
  - Dar, Yaakov
  - Darling, Richard L
  - Darrow, Karl K
  - Darwin, C G
  - Das, T P
  - Daudel, Raymond
  - Dauer, Manning J
  - Daunt, J G
  - Davey, Wheeler P
  - David, Edward E, Jr.
  - Davis, E P
  - Davis, R R
  - Davis, Robert W
  - Davisson, C J
  - Dawson, M R
  - Dearnley, I H
  - Deb, B M
  - De Boer, J
  - Debye, Peter
  - De Carlo, C R
  - De Cicco, Peter
  - Dees, Bowen C
  - De France, Smith J
  - Dekeyser, W
  - Dekker, A J
  - Delaney, Allen Y
  - Delsasso, L P
  - Delta Upsilon Fraternity
  - De Marcus, Wendell
  - Demos, Peter
  - Dennett, Tyler
  - Dennison, David M
  - Deshotels, Warren J
  - Désirant, M
  - Deslattes, Richard D, Jr.
  - Desmond, Thomas C
  - Deutsch, M L
  - Devons, Samuel
  - Devonshire, A F
  - De Vore, Lloyd T
  - Devreese, J T
  - De Vroomen, A R
  - Diamond, Joshua B
  - Dictionary of International Biography
  - Dieke, Gerhard H
  - Dienes, G J
  - Dietz, Albert
  - Digital Computer Laboratory
  - Dill, Dan
  - Dimmock, John O
  - Directory of Research
  - Division of Sponsored research
  - Dodson, Richard
  - Dolan, P D
  - Donahue, J P
  - Donnay, J D H
  - Donnay, Gabrielle
  - Dorsey, N W
  - Doty, Paul
  - Douglass, R H, Jr.
  - Dounay, Gabrielle
  - Dover Publications, Inc.
  - Dow, Henry K
  - Dow, W G
  - Doyle, P A
  - Doyle, William T
  - Dragt, Alex J
  - Drenth, J
  - Dressel, Ralph
  - Dresselhaus, G
  - Drickamer, H G
  - Dropkin, John J
  - Dubois, Jean T
  - DuBridge, Lee A
  - Duchesne, Jules
  - Duffy, Earl G
  - Dufus, Theodore B
  - Du Mond, J W M
  - Duncan, A B F
  - Duncan, M A
  - Duncan, R H
  - Dunlap, W Crawford
    - Materials needs for transportations systems
  - Dunnam, F Eugene
  - Dunnington, F G
  - Du Pont, Pierre S
  - Du Pont Company
  - Durand, W F
  - Dureau, Lionel D
  - Duval, R
  - Dvorak, H R
  - Eagle Enterprises
  - Eastman, George, Research Laboratories for Physics: Dedication
  - Eastman Kodak Company
  - Eberhardt, James J
  - Ebert, C H
  - Eby, John E
  - Ecker, Gunter
  - Ecole Nationale Supérieure des Mines de Saint-Etienne
  - L'Ecole Polytechnique Fédérale de Lausanne
  - Edmiston, Clyde
  - Edwards, Charles W
  - Egli, Paul H
  - Ehrenreich, Henry
  - Ehrenfest, P
  - Einstein, Albert
  - Eirich, Frederick R
  - Eisenhardt, Ewald
  - Eisenhart, Luther Phaler
  - Eisenstein, Julian
  - El Paso Industrial Development Corp.
  - Elder, F V
  - Elder, Joseph D
  - Electrodynamics of ponderable bodies
  - Electronic properties of metals at low temperatures conference, 1958
  - Electronics Corporation of America
  - Eleventh Annual Pittsburgh Diffraction Conference, 1953
  - Ellickson, R T
  - Elliott, Robert S
  - Elliott, Roger J
  - Ellis, Donald E
  - Ellison, Florence R
  - Elsevier Publishing Company
  - Emara, Sayeda
  - Emerson, Eugene S
  - Emtage, P R
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica
  - Encyblopedia Americana
  - Engel, Niels
  - Engineer, Meheryar H
  - Engineering Advisory Committee on Nuclear Science and Engineering
  - Engineering Practice School at Oak Ridge
  - Engineering Supervision Company
  - Engineers Join Council
  - English, E H, Jr.
  - Englman, Robert
  - Enholm, Eric R
  - Epremian, E
  - Epstein, Paul
  - Erlbach, Erich
  - Ernest, John A
  - Eschenfelder, A H
  - Estermann, I
  - Etheridge, J S
  - Etzel, Howard W
  - Eurich, Alvin C
  - Europa Publications Ltd.
  - European Colloquium on current trends in quantum chemistry
  - European Group of Molecular Spectroscopy
  - European Physical Society
  - Euwema, Robert N
  - Evans, Melbourne G
  - Evans, R C
  - Evans, Robley D
  - Everhart, Edgar
  - Ewald, Paul P
  - Executive Assessment Reports
  - Experimental band spectra problems
  - Eyring, Henry
  - Facit, Inc.
  - Faculty Club, MIT
  - Faculty Council, MIT
  - Faessler, A
  - Fairbank, W M
  - Fajans, Kasimir
  - Falcione, Alfred M
  - Fales, John David
  - Falsenfeld, Gary
  - Fan, H Y
  - Fandel, James J
  - Fankuchen, I
  - Fano, U
  - Farnsworth, Dana L
  - Farnsworth, H E
  - Farr, Clarence W
  - Fay Foto Service, Inc.
  - Feigl, Herbert
  - Feigt, Ingmar
  - Feld, B T
    - Discussion of Health Physics
  - Fellows, John A
  - Fermi, Enrico
  - Ferreira, Ricardo
  - Ferroelectrics
  - Ferrous Magnetic Corporation
  - Ferry, Ronald M
  - Feynman, R P
  - Fiegel, Leon J
  - Field, Lamar
  - Fields, W H
  - Fieschi, Roberto
  - Fifth Canadian Symposium on Theoretical Chemistry
  - [Fifth] Coloquio Internacional de Quimicos Teoricos de Expresion Latina
  - Fiftieth Anniversary of the Schrödinger-equation
  - Fine, M E
  - Finland, Maxwell
  - Firemen's Insurance Company
  - First Federal Savings and Loan Ass'n
  - First International Congress of Quantum Chemistry
  - First National Bank of Gainesville
  - Fischer, Louise
  - Fischer-Hjalmars, Inga
  - Fisher, John C
  - Fisk, James
  - Fiske, Milan D
  - Fitzgerald, Edwin R
  - Fitz Patrick
  - Fixman, Marshall
  - Fletcher, Phyllis E
  - Fletcher, R H
  - Fleury, P
  - Flodmark, Stig
  - Floe, Carl F
  - Florida Academy of Sciences
  - Florida Atlantic University
  - Florida. Department of Motor Vehicles
  - Florida Pest Control
  - Florida Southern College
  - Fry, Robert A
  - Flügge, S
  - Fock, V
  - Foderaro, A
  - Foldy, Leslie L
  - Fontana, Peter
  - Ford Foundation
  - Forgacs, O L
  - Fortescue, Richard L
  - Foster, F L
  - Foster, Mrs. Louise
  - Fox, A J
  - Fox, Benjamin
  - Fox, J G
  - Fowler, R H
  - Foyle, Raymond H
  - Frank, Charles
  - Frank, F C
  - Frank, Nathaniel H
  - Franklin, Alan D
  - Franklin Institute
  - Franz, W
  - Franzen, Wolfgang
  - Fratelli Fabbri Editori
  - Frazer, B Chalmers
  - Frechette, V D
  - Frederickson, W R
  - Frederikse, H P R
  - Freedman, Gloria
  - Freeman, Arthur Jay
  - French Lick-Sheraton Hotel
  - French physicists and mathematicians
  - Friauf, Robert J
  - Friden Calculating Machine Company
  - Friedel, Jacques
  - Fritisch, Klaus
  - Fritsche, L
  - Frölich, H
  - Fröman, Anders
  - Froese, Charlotte
  - Frost, Thomas H
  - Frueh, Alfred J, Jr.
  - Fry, Bernard M
  - Fry, John L
  - Fryar, Paul W
  - Frye, J H, Jr.
  - Frye, Sister M. Ignatia
  - Fues, E
  - Fujioka, Yoshio
  - Fujiwara, Takeo
  - Fukushima, Masahisa
  - Fulde, Peter
  - Fuller, Harold Q
  - Fulmer, V A
  - Fumi, F G
  - Fung, B M
  - Fuqua, Don
  - Furniture damaged in move
  - Future of Quantum Chemistry 1976 Symposium
  - Gabriel, J R
  - Gaddoe, Shreedhar R
  - Gaertner, Wolfgang
  - Gainesville [Fla.] Area Chamber of Commerce
  - Gainesville, Fla. Waste Control Division
  - Gallo, Charles
  - Gallup International
  - Galt, John K
  - Garber, M
  - Garland, Carl W
  - Garrison, Allen K
  - Gary, Lee P, Jr.
  - Gaspari, George D
  - Gay, J G
  - Geballe, T H
  - Geddes, R L
  - Gelbart, A
  - Geller, Murray
  - Geller, Seymour
  - General Electric Company
  - General Electric Company Research and Development Center
  - General Motors Corporation
  - General Motors Corp. Research Laboratories
  - Gentile, Arthur C
  - George, William H
  - Gerritsen, A N
  - Getting, I A
  - Gewertz, C E
  - Gibb, Thomas R P, Jr.
  - Gibbs, Peter
  - Gibbs, R C
  - Gibson, John B
  - Gibson, R E
  - Gilat, G
  - Gilbert, T L
  - Gilbert, W W
  - Gilde, Hans-Georg
  - Gill, Stanley J
  - Gilleo, M A
  - Gilliland, E R
  - Gilman, G W
  - Giltrap, G H H
  - Gilvarry, John J
  - Gingrich, Newell S
  - Ginsburg, David
  - Givens, M P
  - Glaser, Frederic M
  - Glazer, Herbert
  - Gmelin Institute. Atomic Energy Documentation Center
  - Godfrey, Edwin W
  - Goldberg, Leo
  - Golden, Sidney
  - Golden, Abraham E
  - Goldhaber, Maurice
  - Golding, R M
  - Goldman, David E
  - Goldman, J E
  - Goldman, Jack
  - Goldsmith, George J
  - Goldstein, L
  - Goldstein, Sydney
  - Gombás, Paul
  - Good, Roland
  - Goodman, Clark
  - Goodrich, Lloyd C
  - Goodwin, H M
  - Gordon and Breach, Science Publishers, Inc.
  - Gordon Research Conferences
  - Gorter, C J
  - Goscinski, Osvaldo
  - Gould, R N
  - Goudsmit, Samuel A
  - Governor Clinto Hotel
  - Gourary, Barry S
  - Graduate Journal
  - Graduate Students in Physics
  - Graf, Otto G
  - Graham, Carolyn
  - Graham, John W
  - Grand Hotel, Krasnapolsky
  - Grant, David M
  - Graves, Harry P
  - Gray, Brian F
  - Greater Boston Physics Calendar
  - Green, Alexander E S
  - Green, Louis C
  - Greene, Jack B
  - Greenshields, John B
  - Gregor, John
  - Greninger, A B
  - Grenville-Wells, H J
  - Gresky, Alan Tolstoy
  - Gressley, Gene M
  - Grigg, Arthur
  - Grimaldi, François
  - Grimshaw, William H
  - Grindlay, John
  - Grinter, L E
  - Grobe, William C
  - Groves, Leslie R
  - Grummitt, Oliver
  - Gruner, Wayne R
  - Grunier, A
  - Gruse, W A
  - Guggenheim, John Simon, Memorial Foundation
  - Guindon, William G
  - Gunning, Harry E
  - Gupta, Babu Lal
  - Gupta, K Das
  - Gutowsky, H S
  - Guttman, Lester
  - Gutweiler, M C
  - Haas, Arthur
  - Hadži, D
  - Hägg, Gunnar
  - Hagedorn, Homer J
  - Hagler, Marion O
  - Hahn, E L
  - Hake, Rodger B
  - Hale, Lester L
  - Hall, Edwin H
  - Hall, Elmer E
  - Hall, George G
  - Hall, T C
  - Halley, J Woods
  - Hallman, L B
  - Halpern, Patricia
  - Hamilton, E P
  - Hampton Court Palace: Supper
  - Handy, Alden G
  - Handsfield, Hugh W
  - Hansen, William W
  - Hansford, R C
  - Hanson, Howard G
  - Hanson, Roger J
  - Hardy, Arthur C
  - Harker, David
  - Harnwell, G P
  - Harman, R Joyce
  - Harries, J H Owen
  - Harris, Frank E
  - Harris, Lawrence
  - Harpers Magazine
  - Harrison, George R
  - Harrison, Gerald
  - Harrison, James F
  - Harrison, Malcolm
  - Harrison, Walter A
  - Hart, Elspeth
  - Hartig, Henry E
  - Hartmann, H
  - Hartree, Douglas R
  - Harvard Foundation for Advanced Study and Research
  - Harvard Graduate Society
  - Harvard Trust Company
  - Harvard University
    - In re: appointment in solid state theory
    - Memorandum on a proposed research program for Jefferson Laboratory
    - Physics Department
  - Harvey, G G
    - Experimental measurements of energy bands in metals as evidenced by soft X-alpha emission
  - Hastie, John W
  - Hastings, Roger Noel
  - Hatfield, Lynn L
  - Hatoyama, George Mitio
  - Havens, W W
  - Havliček, K
  - Hawgood, John
  - Haworth, Leland J
  - Haynes, Sherwood K
  - Hazen, H L
  - Head, Charles E
  - Healea, Monica
  - Healy, A H
  - Heath, H W
  - Heating, piping and air conditioning
  - Heaton, Mrs. Marie
  - Hebb, M H
  - Heber, G
  - Heine, Volker
  - Heidenreich, Robert D
  - Heisenberg, Werner
  - Hellmann, S
  - Helly, Walter
  - Heisenberg, W
  - Henderson, James
  - Henkel, John H
  - Henry, David D
  - Herdel, G F
  - Herman, Frank
  - Herman, Zelek S
  - Herring, Conyers
  - Herweh, A C
  - Herschbach, Dudley
  - Hexter, Robert M
  - Hey, D H
  - Higgins, R J
  - Higgins, Thomas J
  - Hignett, F B
  - Higuchi, Jaro
  - Hijikata, Katsunori
  - Hilberry, Norman
  - Hill, A G
  - Hill, E
  - Hill, E L
  - Hill, Leslie G
  - Hill, Richard K
  - Hinchliffe, Alan
  - Hindley, N K
  - Hindle, W R, Jr.
  - Hinshelwood, C M
  - Hirsch, P B
  - Hirschberg, Joseph G
  - Hirschfelder, Joseph O
  - Hobson, J Peter
  - Hobstetter, J N
  - Hoddeson, Lillian Hartmann
  - Hodge, F W
  - Höhler, G
  - Hoff, H S
  - Hogan, C L
  - Hokanson, W A
  - Holden, Maretta
  - Holland-American Line
  - Hollomon, John H
  - Holt, Evelyn
  - Home Owners Federal Savings and Loan Assn.
  - Honaman, Karl
  - Hooper, Henry O
  - Hopkins, Lewis H
  - Hornig, Donald F
  - Hoshino, Sadao
  - Hosmer, George L
  - Hotel Bellevue
  - Hotel Commodore
  - Hotel Cumberland
  - Hotel Governor Clinton
  - Hotel Manger
  - Hotel Sherman
  - Hotel Suburban
  - Hotel Taft
  - Hotel Victoria Palace
  - Hotel Windermere
  - Hou, Shou-Ling
  - House in Florida, 1964
  - Houston, W V
  - Howland, L Philip
  - Howard, R A
  - Howard University
  - Howarth, D J
  - Howell, Keith M
  - Howell & Sherburne
  - Howland, L Philip
  - Hoyt, Frank C
  - Hsi-teh Shieh, Hilda
  - Hsu, Chang-Pen
  - Hubbard, M M
  - Hückel, E
  - Huggins, Robert A
  - Hughes, Harold K
  - Hughes, Robert E
  - Hughes, Vernon W
  - Huheey, James E
  - Hull, C Max
  - Hull, Gordon F
  - Hume-Rothery, W
  - Humphrey, Hubert H
  - Hunneman and Company
  - Hunsaker, J C
  - Hunt, Gordon C
  - Hunter, Geoffrey
  - Huntington, H B
  - Huntoon, R D
  - Huntington, Mrs. Louise
  - Hurley, Andrew C
  - Hurst, Robert PHusimi, Kōdi
  - Hutchinson, W Spencer
  - Hutchison, Clyde A
  - Hutchisson, Elmer
  - Hyde, Melvin W
  - Iball, John
  - Ibers, James A
  - I'Haya, Y J
  - Ilahi, Karam
  - Iliffe, John K
  - Iliffe Books Ltd
  - Imperial House Motel, Lexington, Ky.
  - Ingalls, Robert L
  - Ing-Nan-Chiu
  - Inoue, Takeshi
  - Inskeep, Richard G
  - Inspec Matters
  - Institute for Advanced Study
  - Institute for Defense Analyses
  - Institute for Scientific Information
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers
  - Institute of International Education
  - Internal Revenue Service
  - International Academy of Quantum Molecular Science
  - International Business Machines Corporation
  - International Commission of Optics
  - International Conference on Lattice Dynamics
  - International Conference on curren problems in crystal physics
  - International Conference on Physics Education
  - International Conference on Physics of Metals
  - International Conference on Semiconductors
  - International Conference on the metal-nonmetal transition
  - International Conference on the physics of Semiconductors
  - International Conference on Theoretical Physics
  - International Congress on Magnetism
  - International Council of Scientific Unions
  - International Journal of Quantum Chemistry
  - International Journal of the Physics and Chemistry of Solids
  - International Platform Ass'n
  - International Science Foundation
  - International Symposium on Atomic and Molecular Quantum Theory in Honor of R. S. Mulliken
  - International Symposium on Solid State Physics
  - International Union of Crystallography
  - International Union of Pure and Applied Physics
  - Inter-University Committee on Travel Grants
  - Inter-University Council for Higher Education Overseas
  - Inui, Teturo
  - Irradiation Damage Committee Conference
  - Ireland, William J
  - Isakson, Frank B
  - Ishiguro, Eiichi
  - Iwanaga, Kenzo
  - Jaccarino, Vincent
  - Jackson, Dugald C
  - Jackson, F B
  - Jackson, Harold R
  - Jacobs, Verne L
  - Jacobsen, Edward H
  - Jaeger, Zeev
  - Jeffe, Hans H
  - Jaffe, L D
  - Jaggi, Martin
  - James, Hubert M
  - James, Mrs. Hubert M
  - James, Robert P
  - Jammer, Max
  - Jannussis, A
  - Jansen, L
  - Jette, Eric R
  - Jewett, Frank B
  - Jirgal, George H, Jr.
  - Jorgensen, Chr Klixbüll
  - John Hancock Mutual Life Ins. Co.
  - Johns, Martin W
  - Johnson, Adger S
  - Johnson, Keith H
    - Electronic structure and function of metal ions in biomolecules and bio-materials
    - Recent applications of the SCF-X-alpha scattered wave method to systems of catalytic and biocatalytic importance
  - Johnson, M H
  - Johnson, Malcolm
  - Johnson, Oliver
  - Johnson, T H
  - Johnson, W E
  - Johnson, Walter R
  - Johnston, H L
  - Johnson, L H
  - Joint Commission for Spectroscopy
  - Jonassen, Hans 3
  - Jones, Ernest
  - Jones, Howard M
  - Joshi, A W
  - Joshi, Bhairav D
  - Jossem, E L
  - Jost, Res
  - Journal of Chemical Physics
  - Journal of Computational Physics
  - Journal of Mathematical Physics
  - Journal of Physical Chemistry
  - Journal of the American Chemical Society
  - Journal of the Franklin Institute
  - Joyce, Madeline
  - Judd, Brian R
  - Judd, Deane B
  - Jurá˘s, Vladimic
  - Juretschke, Hellmut J
  - Kakiuchi, Yoshinobu
  - Kansa, Edward J
  - Kantowski, Ronald
  - Kantrowitz, Adrian
  - Kaplan, Harvey
  - Kalbacher, Barbara J
  - Kern, C W
  - Karo, Arnold M
  - Karr, Lyman W
  - Karreman, George
  - Kasha, Michael
  - Kashyap, B M S
  - Kastler, A
  - Katcher, David A
  - Kauffmann, D R
  - Kaufmann, A R
  - Kaufman, Joyce J
  - Kauzmann, Walter
  - Keating, Frank A
  - Kelly, M J
  - Keller, Alton H
  - Kelly, Hugh P
  - Kelly, Marvin J
  - Kelso, James G
  - Kemble, E C
  - Kenkre, V M
  - Kennard, Ralph B
  - Kennedy, E J, Jr.
  - Kenney, J F
  - Kentucky Hotel
  - Keohan, E J
  - Keown, E R
  - Keown, Ray
  - Kerker, Milton
  - Kern, C William
  - Kern, E D
  - Kessler, J
  - Kessler, John O
  - Keyes, Frederick G
  - Khubchandani, P G
  - Kieffer, William F
  - Kikuchi, Ryoichi
  - Killian, James Rhyne, Jr.
  - Killian, Thomas J
  - Kim, Dong-Yun
  - Kim, Yong Duk
  - Kimball, G E
  - Kimball, Herbert H
  - Kincaid, John F
  - King, J S, Jr.
  - King, Katherine
  - Kinnecom, Paul Wesley
  - Kip, Arthur F
  - Kirkman, R W
  - Kirkpatrick, Donald E
  - Kirkpatrick, Paul
  - Kirkwood, John G
  - Kiser, R W
  - Kispert, M G
  - Kistiakowsky, George B
  - Kistler, S S
  - Kittel, Charles
  - Kitz, Adolf
  - Kleinberg, Jacob
  - Kleiner, Walter H
  - Klingbeil, Ralph
  - Klopman, G
  - Klug, Harold P
  - Kmetko, Edward A
  - Knauss, Harold P
  - Kneale, E H
  - Knight, Paula G
  - Knobel, Max
  - Kobayashi, Kenji
  - Koch, H
  - Koch, Jorgen
  - Knopoff
  - Knox, W J
  - Koehler, W C
  - Koga, Yukiyoshi
  - Kohn, Grace
  - Kohn, Walter
  - Kolbe, Parke R
  - Koozekanani, Said
  - Kopelman, Raoul
  - Kopp, E W
  - Korringa, Jan
  - Kobayasi, Sy[ocirc]it
  - Koshuba, Walter J
  - Koster, George Fred
  - Kosting, Peter R
  - Kotani, Masao
  - Koutecky, J
  - Kouvelites, James S
  - Kovel, Steven M
  - Kraichman, Robert H
  - Kramers, Hans
  - Krishnan, K S
  - Kronig, R de L
  - Kruger, P Gerald
  - Krumhansl, J A
  - Krutter, H M
  - Ky, Y H
  - Kuebler, Clark G
  - Kuehn, E C, Jr.
  - Kuehnlenz, Gary
  - Kuhn, Thomas S
  - Kumagai, Hiroo
  - Kunstelj, D
  - Kuper, Mariette
  - Kursunoglu, Behram
  - Kwo, William T
  - La Bahn, Ray
  - Laboratory of Molecular Structure and Spectra
  - Ladenburg, R
  - Lafon, Earl E
  - Laforgue, Alex
  - Lamb, Arthur B
  - La Morte, M F
  - Lancaster Press
  - Land, Edwin H
  - Landry, Paul E
  - Landsberg, Peter E
  - Lane, C T
  - Lane, W H, Jr.
  - Langer, R M
  - Langley, E F
  - Langiulli, Anne
  - Lapp, C J
  - Lark-Horovitz, K
  - Larson, Allen C
  - Larson, Linea
  - Lassiter, Roy L, Jr.
  - Laue, Hans
  - Laval, Jean
  - Lawrence, Ernest O
  - Lawson, A W, Jr.
  - Lax, Benjamin
  - Lax, Melvin
  - Lazonby, Dell, Graham, Willcox & Barber
  - Leberrigue, M A
  - Lebovitz, Shirley Ann
  - Lebowitz, Joel L
  - Le Corre, Y
  - Lectures, 1929
  - Lee, Ching Tsung
  - Lee, Henry Uy
  - Lee, Keum Ju
  - Lee, Paul F
  - Lee, T H
  - Lee, W B
  - Lee Memorial Hospital
  - Lehman, Guy W
  - Leman, Gunnar
  - Lemonick, Aaron
  - Lemos, Anthony M
  - Lendrum, J T
  - Lennard-Jones, John
  - Le Roy, D J
  - Le Roy, G
  - Leurgans, Paul
  - Levy, H A
  - Lewis, H. K., & Company
  - Lewis, Lester Clark
  - Lewis, W K
  - Li, James C M
  - Liberman, David
  - Lichnerowicz
  - Lichtensteiger, Manfred A
  - Lidiard, Alan Bernard
  - Liebhold, Klaus G
  - Liehr, Andrew D
  - Lillie, D W
  - Lin, Chun C
  - Lincoln Laboratory
  - Linderberg, Jan
  - Lindgren, Ingvar
  - Lindgren, Waldemar
  - Lindholm, Einar
  - Lineberger, W Carl
  - Lipscomb, W N
  - Liss, Alan R
  - Livingston, M Stanley
  - Lloyd, R M A
  - Lo, Yi-Chao M
  - Locke, Mary J
  - Locke, William N
  - Lockett, Albert
  - Lockwood, J A
  - Loeb, Leonard
  - Loebl, Ernest M
  - Löwdin, Per-Olov
    - The Quantum Theory project
    - Some aspects on the American-Swedish exchange in quantum sciences
  - Lofgren, David
  - Lomer, W M
  - Lomont, John S
  - London, F W
  - Londono, J H
  - Longuet-Higgins, H Christopher
  - Lonsdale, Kathleen
  - London University
  - Loomis, Alfred L
  - Loomis, F W
  - Loomis, Wheeler
  - Lopuszanski, Jan T
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory
  - Loucks, Terry L
  - Lowan, Arnold N
  - Lowde, R D
  - Loyola University in New Orleans
  - Luck, David A E
  - Luckman, Charles
  - Ludloff, J F
  - Lukasik, Stephen J
  - Lundqvist, Stig
  - Lutz, Charles H
  - Luttinger, J
  - Lyman, Theodore
  - Maas, M
  - McAdow, Madeleine
  - MacAllister, J
  - McAvey, William L
  - McClure, Donald S
  - McClure, J W
  - McClure, Joel W
  - McCollough, Robert H
  - McCombie, C W
  - McDaniel, Boyce D
  - McDaniel, Paul W
  - MacDonald, D K C
  - MacDonald, Gordon J F
  - McDougall, J M
  - McDowell, Charles A
  - MacDowell, Mrs. Grace P
  - McElroy, M C
  - MacFarlane, G C
  - MacGillavry, C H
  - McGlinn, William D
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, Inc.
  - McHargue, Carl J
  - McHenry, E
  - Mac Inness, D A
  - McIntosh, R
  - MacIntyre, Alice
  - Mack, Evelyn
  - Mack, Julian
  - McKenna, William W
  - McKenzie, Lawson M
  - McKinnon, J C
  - MacLaurin, R C
  - McMillan, W G
  - McMillen, Edwin M
  - McMillin, J B
  - McNally, Rand
  - MacPherson, H G
  - McWeeny, Roy
  - Madison, Herbert C
  - Mahadeva, N
  - Mahoney, R C
  - Maier, Leonard C
  - Mailing lists
  - Malhiot, R J
  - Malli, Gulzari Lal
  - Maltby, Wilson R
  - Mangelsdorf, P C
  - Mangus Organ Corporation
  - Manley, J H
  - Mann, Joseph B
  - Manning, Ellis L
  - Manning, Millard F
  - Many Body Problem Symposium
  - Mapleton, Robert A
  - Maradudin, A
  - March, Norman
  - Marchant Calculating Machine
  - Marcus, Jules A
  - Marcus, Paul M
  - Margenav, Henry
  - Marginau, Henry
  - Markham, C H
  - Markham, Jordan J
  - Marshak, R E
  - Marshall, Adele K
  - Marshall, Walter
  - Martin, Frederick Roy
  - Martin, J L
  - Martin, R P
  - Martin, Stuart T
  - Martino, Frank
  - Martinozzoli, Armando
  - Marton, L
  - Massachusetts Department of Corporations and Taxation
  - Massachusetts Income Tax Bureau
  - Massachusetts Registry of Motor Vehicles
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
    - Administrative Assignments
    - Advanced research projects agency
    - Appointment of assistant chancellors
    - Budget
    - Bursar
    - Chemical and Solid-State Physics
    - Committee on the Rockefeller Fund
    - Computation Center
    - Conditions of a new plan of appointment of Professors, etc.
    - Conference on molecular quantum mechanics
    - Department of Chemical Engineering
    - Department of Mechanical Engineering
    - Department of Physics (see also: MIT,and MIT. Physics Department)
    - Division of Industrial Cooperation
    - Division of Sponsored Research
    - Elective Folder
    - Emeriti
    - Faculty Council
    - Heads of Departments
    - High Voltage project of the Physics Dept.
    - Inauguration of K.T.Compton as President
    - Joint Computing report
    - Joint project committee on properties of matter.
    - Joint seminar
    - Laboratory for nuclear science and engineering.
    - Laboratory for nuclear science and engineering. Steering committee.
    - Library
    - Members of the Staff
    - New building space
    - New magnet facility
    - Notice of committee meeting
    - Nuclear committee
    - Office memos
    - Office supplies - invoices
    - Outline of the proposed basic 600 series
    - Permanent historical exhibit
    - Personnel office
    - Physical sciences division
    - Physics department - equipment
    - PressProgram
    - Program reports